the software to any third party without Microsoft’s prior written approval; • 
work around any technical limitations in the software; • reverse engineer, 
decompile or disassemble the software, except and only to the extent that 
applicable law expressly permits, despite this limitation; • make more copies of 
the software than specified in this agreement or allowed by applicable law, 
despite this limitation; • publish the software for others to copy; • rent, 
lease or lend the software; • transfer the software or this agreement to any 
third party; or • use the software for commercial software hosting services. 7. 
EXPORT RESTRICTIONS. The software is subject to United States export laws and 
regulations. You must comply with all domestic and international export laws and 
regulations that apply to the software. These laws include restrictions on 
destinations, end users and end use. For additional information, see 
www.microsoft.com/exporting. 8. SUPPORT SERVICES. Because this software is “as 
is,” we may not provide support services for it. 9. ENTIRE AGREEMENT. This 
agreement, and the terms for supplements, updates, Internet-based services and 
support services that you use, are the entire agreement for the software and 
support services. 10. APPLICABLE LAW. a. United States. If you acquired the 
software in the United States, Washington state law governs the interpretation 
of this agreement and applies to claims for breach of it, regardless of conflict 
of laws principles. The laws of the state where you live govern all other 
claims, including claims under state consumer protection laws, unfair 
competition laws, and in tort. b. Outside the United States. If you acquired the 
software in any other country, the laws of that country apply. 11. LEGAL EFFECT. 
This agreement describes certain legal rights. You may have other rights under 
the laws of your country. You may also have rights with respect to the party 
from whom you acquired the software. This agreement does not change your rights 
under the laws of your country if the laws of your country do not permit it to 
do so. 12. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY. THE SOFTWARE IS LICENSED “AS-IS.” YOU BEAR 
THE RISK OF USING IT. MICROSOFT GIVES NO EXPRESS WARRANTIES, GUARANTEES OR 
CONDITIONS. YOU MAY HAVE ADDITIONAL CONSUMER RIGHTS UNDER YOUR LOCAL LAWS WHICH 
THIS AGREEMENT CANNOT CHANGE. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER YOUR LOCAL LAWS, 
MICROSOFT EXCLUDES THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A 
PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. 13. LIMITATION ON AND EXCLUSION OF 
REMEDIES AND DAMAGES. YOU CAN RECOVER FROM MICROSOFT AND ITS SUPPLIERS ONLY 
DIRECT DAMAGES UP TO U.S. $5.00. YOU CANNOT RECOVER ANY OTHER DAMAGES, INCLUDING 
CONSEQUENTIAL, LOST PROFITS, SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES. This 
limitation applies to • anything related to the software, services, content 
(including code) on third party Internet sites, or third party programs; and • 
claims for breach of contract, breach of warranty, guarantee or condition, 
strict liability, negligence, or other tort to the extent permitted by 
applicable law. It also applies even if Microsoft knew or should have known 
about the possibility of the damages. The above limitation or exclusion may not 
apply to you because your country may not allow the exclusion or limitation of 
incidental, consequential or other damages. Please note: As this software is 
distributed in Quebec, Canada, some of the clauses in this agreement are 
provided below in French. Remarque : Ce logiciel étant distribué au Québec, 
Canada, certaines des clauses dans ce contrat sont fournies ci-dessous en 
français. EXONÉRATION DE GARANTIE. Le logiciel visé par une licence est offert « 
tel quel ». Toute utilisation de ce logiciel est à votre seule risque et péril. 
Microsoft n’accorde aucune autre garantie expresse. Vous pouvez bénéficier de 
droits additionnels en vertu du droit local sur la protection des consommateurs, 
que ce contrat ne peut modifier. La ou elles sont permises par le droit locale, 
les garanties implicites de qualité marchande, d’adéquation à un usage 
particulier et d’absence de contrefaçon sont exclues. LIMITATION DES 
DOMMAGES-INTÉRÊTS ET EXCLUSION DE RESPONSABILITÉ POUR LES DOMMAGES. Vous pouvez 
obtenir de Microsoft et de ses fournisseurs une indemnisation en cas de dommages 
directs uniquement à hauteur de 5,00 $ US. Vous ne pouvez prétendre à aucune 
indemnisation pour les autres dommages, y compris les dommages spéciaux, 
indirects ou accessoires et pertes de bénéfices. Cette limitation concerne : • 
tout ce qui est relié au logiciel, aux services ou au contenu (y compris le 
code) figurant sur des sites Internet tiers ou dans des programmes tiers ; et • 
les réclamations au titre de violation de contrat ou de garantie, ou au titre de 
responsabilité stricte, de négligence ou d’une autre faute dans la limite 
autorisée par la loi en vigueur. Elle s’applique également, même si Microsoft 
connaissait ou devrait connaître l’éventualité d’un tel dommage. Si votre pays 
n’autorise pas l’exclusion ou la limitation de responsabilité pour les dommages 
indirects, accessoires ou de quelque nature que ce soit, il se peut que la 
limitation ou l’exclusion ci-dessus ne s’appliquera pas à votre égard. EFFET 
JURIDIQUE. Le présent contrat décrit certains droits juridiques. Vous pourriez 
avoir d’autres droits prévus par les lois de votre pays. Le présent contrat ne 
modifie pas les droits que vous confèrent les lois de votre pays si celles-ci ne 
le permettent pas. 