cancel them at any time. 3. TIME-SENSITIVE SOFTWARE. The software will stop 
running on 15 March 2008. You will not receive any other notice. You may not be 
able to access data used with the software when it stops running. 4. PRE-RELEASE 
SOFTWARE. This software is a pre-release version. It may not work the way a 
final version of the software will. We may change it for the final, commercial 
version. We also may not release a commercial version. 5. FEEDBACK. If you give 
feedback about the software to Microsoft, you give to Microsoft, without charge, 
the right to use, share and commercialize your feedback in any way and for any 
purpose. You also give to third parties, without charge, any patent rights 
needed for
This agreement describes certain legal rights. You may have other rights under 
the laws of your country. You may also have rights with respect to the party 
from whom you acquired the software. This agreement does not change your rights 
under the laws of your country if the laws of your country do not permit it to 
do so. 12. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY. THE SOFTWARE IS LICENSED “AS-IS.” YOU BEAR 
THE RISK OF USING IT. MICROSOFT GIVES NO EXPRESS WARRANTIES, GUARANTEES OR 
CONDITIONS. YOU MAY HAVE ADDITIONAL CONSUMER RIGHTS UNDER YOUR LOCAL LAWS WHICH 
THIS AGREEMENT CANNOT CHANGE. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER YOUR LOCAL LAWS, 
MICROSOFT EXCLUDES THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A 
PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. 13. LIMITATION ON AND EXCLUSION OF 
REMEDIES AND DAMAGES. YOU CAN RECOVER FROM MICROSOFT AND ITS SUPPLIERS ONLY 
DIRECT DAMAGES UP TO U.S. $5.00. YOU CANNOT RECOVER ANY OTHER DAMAGES, INCLUDING 
CONSEQUENTIAL, LOST PROFITS, SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES. This 
limitation applies to • anything related to the software, services, content 
(including code) on third party Internet sites, or third party programs; and • 
claims for breach of contract, breach of warranty, guarantee or condition, 
strict liability, negligence, or other tort to the extent permitted by 
applicable law. It also applies even if Microsoft knew or should have known 
about the possibility of the damages. The above limitation or exclusion may not 
apply to you because your country may not allow the exclusion or limitation of 
incidental, consequential or other damages. Please note: As this software is 
distributed in Quebec, Canada, some of the clauses in this agreement are 
provided below in French. Remarque : Ce logiciel étant distribué au Québec, 
Canada, certaines des clauses dans ce contrat sont fournies ci-dessous en 
français. EXONÉRATION DE GARANTIE. Le logiciel visé par une licence est offert « 
tel quel ». Toute utilisation de ce logiciel est à votre seule risque et péril. 
Microsoft n’accorde aucune autre garantie expresse. Vous pouvez bénéficier de 
droits additionnels en vertu du droit local sur la protection des consommateurs, 
que ce contrat ne peut modifier. La ou elles sont permises par le droit locale, 
les garanties implicites de qualité marchande, d’adéquation à un usage 
particulier et d’absence de contrefaçon sont exclues. LIMITATION DES 
DOMMAGES-INTÉRÊTS ET EXCLUSION DE RESPONSABILITÉ POUR LES DOMMAGES. Vous pouvez 
obtenir de Microsoft et de ses fournisseurs une indemnisation en cas de dommages 
directs uniquement à hauteur de 5,00 $ US. Vous ne pouvez prétendre à aucune 
indemnisation pour les autres dommages, y compris les dommages spéciaux, 
indirects ou accessoires et pertes de bénéfices. Cette limitation concerne : • 
tout ce qui est relié au logiciel, aux services ou au contenu (y compris le 
code) figurant sur des sites Internet tiers ou dans des programmes tiers ; et • 
les réclamations au titre de violation de contrat ou de garantie, ou au titre de 
responsabilité stricte, de négligence ou d’une autre faute dans la limite 
autorisée par la loi en vigueur. Elle s’applique également, même si Microsoft 
connaissait ou devrait connaître l’éventualité d’un tel dommage. Si votre pays 
n’autorise pas l’exclusion ou la limitation de responsabilité pour les dommages 
indirects, accessoires ou de quelque nature que ce soit, il se peut que la 
limitation ou l’exclusion ci-dessus ne s’appliquera pas à votre égard. EFFET 
JURIDIQUE. Le présent contrat décrit certains droits juridiques. Vous pourriez 
avoir d’autres droits prévus par les lois de votre pays. Le présent contrat ne 
modifie pas les droits que vous confèrent les lois de votre pays si celles-ci ne 
le permettent pas. 